Mystery takes center stage!
Scooby-Doo! Stage Fright is a family, adventure,
animation film directed by Victor Cook.
Join Scooby-Doo, Shaggy and the Mystery Inc.
crew as they head to Chicago for Talent Star, a hit talent show in
which Fred and Daphne are finalists with some high hopes.
Unlucky for them, the competition is frightful as the show is being broadcast from an opera house with a
history of horrors and a particularly vengeful phantom that has cursed the show's production.
Scooby-Doo / Fred (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Velma (voice), played by Mindy Cohn.
Daphne (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Shaggy (voice), played by Matthew Lillard.
Emma Gale (voice), played by Isabella Acres.
The Phantom / Lance Damon (voice), played by Troy Baker.
Scooby-Doo!
Stage Fright is a 2013 direct-to-DVD animated musical comedy horror film, and the
twenty-first entry in the direct-to-video series of Scooby-Doo films.
It was released on August 20, 2013, by Warner Premiere, the last film to be
released under this label due to its dissolution the previous year.
The movie made its linear premiere on Cartoon Network
in the United States on March 25, 2023.
The film explores themes of monster, talking dog, cartoon dog.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.